http://www.glassybaby.com/privacy-policy

we are experiencing high order volumes - see shipping details
your privacy: overview
this privacy policy (this “privacy policy”) sets out the privacy policies and practices for glassybaby llc (“glassybaby”) with respect to how glassybaby collects personal information. it also describes how glassybaby maintains, uses, and discloses personal information. this privacy policy applies to information collected from you by glassybaby via this website and other websites operated or provided by glassybaby, including www.glassybaby.com and various subdomains (collectively, the “sites”), and our retail stores, including the hot shop workshop (collectively, the “stores”), as well as any other applications or services that display this policy (collectively, the “services”), and other places where or means by which we may collect personal information. this privacy policy also sets out how you can access certain information that glassybaby may collect about you. in this privacy policy, “personal information” means information or opinion about an individual whose identity is apparent or can be reasonably ascertained from the information or opinion as further defined under applicable privacy laws, including, but not limited to, your contacts and other personal information collected through the services.
please note that the sites may contain links to other third party websites that are not controlled or operated by glassybaby. this privacy policy does not apply to such third party websites, and glassybaby is not responsible for the content of such third party websites or the privacy practices of such third parties. therefore glassybaby encourages you to request and review the privacy policies of any third parties before disclosing your personal information to such parties or when visiting such third party websites.
1. consent
by submitting personal information to glassybaby or its service providers and agents, you agree that glassybaby may collect your personal information and you consent to the use, disclosure and transfer of your personal information in accordance with this privacy policy and as permitted or required by law. subject to legal and contractual requirements, you may refuse or withdraw your consent to certain of the purposes identified herein at any time by contacting glassybaby at the address provided below. if you refuse or withdraw your consent, you acknowledge that glassybaby may not be able to provide you or continue to provide you with certain services or information which may be of value to you.
2. revisions to this privacy policy
glassybaby reserves the right, in glassybaby’s discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this privacy policy at any time and from time to time, without prior notice to you. however, glassybaby will treat your continued use of the sites and services following such revision as your acceptance of the revised terms. all revisions will be posted to the sites and will apply to any personal information collected on or after the date posted. glassybaby will obtain the necessary consents required under applicable privacy laws if it seeks to collect, use or disclose your personal information for purposes other than those to which consent has been obtained unless otherwise required or permitted by law.
this privacy policy was last updated september 14, 2016.
3. collection of your information
glassybaby may collect personal information in connection with your use or purchase of glassybaby’s products and services, including at the stores or the sites or through your use of the services, which may include information provided in connection with the following activities:
registering or filling in forms on the sites or in the stores. this includes information you may provide when you request additional information about glassybaby’s products and services or sign up to receive glassybaby’s e-mail newsletters or coupons.
completing a profile or uploading content to the sites.
purchasing any product or service from glassybaby, whether at the stores or the sites.
providing design or product feedback or making other submissions to glassybaby.
requesting information or assistance from glassybaby. glassybaby may also keep a copy of any communications or correspondence you may send to it, including any e-mail communications.
participating or responding to consumer survey or requests for consumer’s opinions, concerns, and preferences regarding glassybaby’s products and services.
participating in consumer contests, sweepstakes and other promotions.
using other features of the sites or services that may be offered from time to time, and may require such information in order to utilize the feature (including but not limited to making a submission as defined in the terms of use).
the personal information that glassybaby may collect may include your name, username, password, email address, age, date of birth, gender, address, telephone number, credit card and debit card numbers (with expiration dates), personal preferences, and any other personal information that you choose to include in your profile, your submissions of your goals to glassybaby, or in other communications to glassybaby. you represent and warrant that you have the right and authority or have obtained all necessary consents to provide any information, including any personal information of another individual that is provided by you to glassybaby.
glassybaby may also collect information that may not be personal information, which may include, but is not limited to, the frequency of user visits to the sites and services, the routes by which users access the sites and services and use of any hyperlinks available on the sites and services. glassybaby or its service providers and agents may process and use this aggregate data for various purposes including, but not limited to, analysis of this data for trends and statistics, development of the sites and services and the sites’ and services’ features and offerings, assessing patterns of use, or planning and evaluating marketing initiatives. this information is gathered by certain tools and methods such as the collection of your ip address or the use of cookies and is maintained, used and disclosed in aggregate form unless otherwise noted.
4. cookies
like many websites, glassybaby utilizes “cookies” to maintain a record of your visit to the sites and your use of the services. a cookie is a small text file that is transferred by a web server and stored on the hard drive of your computer or mobile device. it can only be read by the server that sent it to you. this information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous unless you have otherwise provided glassybaby with personal information.
cookies help glassybaby to improve the sites and services, and to deliver more personalized service by enabling glassybaby to estimate audience size and usage patterns; to store information about your preferences; to speed up your searches and to recognize you when you return to the sites or use the services.
most web browsers automatically accept cookies. if you would prefer to prevent your computer from accepting glassybaby’s cookies, you may follow your internet browser’s steps for doing so. please note, however, that if you do disable cookies from your browser, you may not be able to access certain sections of the sites or the services.
5. ip addresses
an ip address is a computer's numeric address, by which it can be located within a network. glassybaby may record your ip address when you visit or use services or features on the sites. glassybaby may use your ip address for the purposes noted above, and also to help diagnose problems with glassybaby’s server, or to administer the sites. glassybaby may also use your ip address to identify you when glassybaby feels it is necessary to enforce compliance with this privacy policy or the terms of use, or to protect the sites, services, systems, information, employees, service providers, business partners, users, customers and others.
6. protection of your information
to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, maintain data accuracy and facilitate the appropriate use of information, glassybaby uses physical, technological and administrative procedures to protect the personal information that glassybaby collects from loss, unauthorized access, modification, disclosure or other misuse.
nevertheless, internet or wireless transmissions are never completely private or secure. you understand that any messages or information you send to the sites or through the services may be read or intercepted by others. if you have any questions about the security of personal information collected by glassybaby, please contact customerservice@glassbaby.com.
you should also be aware that certain aspects of the sites and services are not confidential and are available for public viewing. for example, other users of the sites and services will be able to view your profile and goals that are publically available. any submissions that you may post to any publicly available blogs or other publicly available features of the sites and services are not confidential and may be viewed by other users of the sites and services. by making personal information publicly available where the sites and services allow you to do so, you consent to such publication by glassybaby or its service providers and agents. please refer to the terms of use for additional provisions relating to user submissions that may apply to you.
7. use of your personal information
upon glassybaby’s collection of your personal information, glassybaby may use such personal information internally, separately or in combination with pre-existing information, for the following purposes:
to develop, enhance, market, sell or otherwise provide information, products or services
to establish and conduct commercial relationships, including to process purchases or other transactions and to conduct or administer other transactions that you may engage in with glassybaby including at the stores, through the sites or the services;
to conduct or administer contests, sweepstakes or other promotions in which you have participated;
to contact you and to respond to any communications that you may have had with us;
to troubleshoot problems with the sites and services;
to customize your experience or homepage on the sites;
to develop and manage glassybaby's business and operations;
to enforce glassybaby’s terms of use or comply with this privacy policy;
to detect and protect glassybaby and other third parties against error, negligence, breach of contract, fraud, theft and other illegal activity, and to audit compliance with glassybaby’s policies and contractual obligations;
to engage in business transactions, including the purchase, sale, lease, merger, amalgamation or any other type of acquisition, disposal, securitization or financing involving glassybaby;
as permitted by, and to comply with, any legal or regulatory requirements or provisions;
to access, preserve, disclose and use your personal information contained in your account, all submissions (as defined in the terms of use), all communications to and from you, all information relating to your use of the sites, if glassybaby is required to do so by law or legal process or if glassybaby determines, in its sole discretion, that such action is necessary to protect the rights of glassybaby, third parties, and other users of the sites or for purposes of responding to your request for customer service; or
for any other purpose to which you consent.
personal information collected by glassybaby may be transferred to, stored and processed in the united states or other jurisdictions worldwide. if located in another jurisdiction for processing or other reason, the information may be accessed by the courts, law enforcement, and national security authorities of that jurisdiction.
8. disclosure of your information
glassybaby may disclose your personal information to its subsidiaries or affiliates and to third parties whom glassybaby hires to provide services on glassybaby’s behalf, including, but not limited to, support services, website services, delivering promotional materials, contests, sweepstakes and other promotions, and answering customer questions about glassybaby’s products and services. these subsidiaries, affiliates and third parties may be located overseas. glassybaby will only provide those third parties with the personal information that they need to deliver the services to glassybaby and/or on glassybaby’s behalf. glassybaby will not disclose your personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes without obtaining prior affirmative consent. in the event that glassybaby is involved in a business transaction, including the purchase, sale, lease, merger, amalgamation or any other type of acquisition, disposal, securitization or financing involving glassybaby, you consent to your personal information and any other information glassybaby may have collected being transferred to another party in connection with such transaction. you also consent to glassybaby disclosing your personal information to legal, financial, insurance, or other advisors in connection with such business transaction or management of all or part of glassybaby’s business or operations; as consented to by you from time to time, including to fulfill any other purposes that are identified when the personal information is collected; or as otherwise permitted or required by law.
california civil code section 1798.83 entitles california customers to request information concerning whether a business has disclosed personal information to any third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. glassybaby will not sell or share your personal information with non-glassybaby companies for their direct marketing purposes without your affirmative consent. california customers who wish to request further information about our compliance with this law or have questions or concerns about this privacy policy and the terms of use may contact customerservice@glassybaby.com.
9. retention of your personal information
the personal information that you provide will be retained by glassybaby in accordance with applicable laws. however, glassybaby will take reasonable steps to destroy or permanently de-identify personal information it holds if it is no longer needed for glassybaby’s business purposes.
10. children's privacy
glassybaby recognizes the privacy interests of children and glassybaby encourages parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. the sites are not intended for children under the age of 18. glassybaby does not target its services or the sites to children under 18. glassybaby does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 18.
11. choice and opt-out preferences
glassybaby does not collect your personal information unless you choose to provide it. if, at any time, you prefer not to receive further email communications from glassybaby (except in connection with information, products or services that you specifically request), you will have the ability to unsubscribe from such communications by means of a link provided in every broadcast e-mail that is sent to you by glassybaby. if, at any time, you prefer not to receive any other form of communication from glassybaby, you will have the ability to unsubscribe from such communications by contacting customerservice@glassybaby.com.
12. access and correction
glassybaby will take reasonable steps to ensure the personal information it holds is accurate, complete and up to date. upon your written request, subject to certain exceptions provided by law, glassybaby will inform you of the existence, use and disclosure of your personal information and give you access to that information. additionally, if you have any questions or enquiries relating to our privacy practices or procedures, or if you believe that the personal information that glassybaby holds about you is not accurate, complete or up to date you may write to the privacy officer at the address provided below. if you are able to establish that the information is not accurate, complete or up to date, glassybaby will take reasonable steps to correct the information so that it is accurate, complete and up to date.
13. no guarantees
while this privacy policy states standards for maintenance of data, and while efforts will be made to meet these standards, glassybaby does not guarantee that it will comply with these standards. there may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. consequently, we offer no warranties or representations regarding the maintenance or non-disclosure of data.
14. request for access and correction, questions or comments
glassybaby welcomes questions and comments about this privacy policy. requests for access and correction of your personal information, and questions or comments should be directed to customerservice@glassybaby.com.
